[
  {
    "id": 21,
    "question": "Which muscle supinates?",
    "options": {
      "a": "biceps brachii",
      "b": "brachialis",
      "c": "triceps brachii"
    },
    "correct_option": "a",
    "correct_answer_text": null
  },
  {
    "id": 22,
    "question": "Which muscle is most superior on the axilary border of the scapula?",
    "options": {
      "a": "teres major",
      "b": "teres minor",
      "c": "serratus anterior"
    },
    "correct_option": "b",
    "correct_answer_text": null
  },
  {
    "id": 23,
    "question": "Which muscle best counteracts posturally round shoulders?",
    "options": {
      "a": "pec minor",
      "b": "rhomboids",
      "c": "ant. deltoid",
      "d": "infraspinatus"
    },
    "correct_option": "b",
    "correct_answer_text": null
  },
  {
    "id": 24,
    "question": "Where do fight or flight impulses come from in the vertebral column?",
    "options": {
      "a": "thoracolumbar",
      "b": "craniosacral",
      "c": "cervical"
    },
    "correct_option": "a",
    "correct_answer_text": null
  },
  {
    "id": 25,
    "question": "Stimulation of the musculocutaneous nerve causes which action?",
    "options": {
      "a": "flexion of elbow",
      "b": "extension of elbow",
      "c": "dorsiflexion of ankle"
    },
    "correct_option": "a",
    "correct_answer_text": null
  },
  {
    "id": 26,
    "question": "A runner has pain in his hip and knee when flexing and extending the thigh (when running). Which muscle is involved?",
    "options": {
      "a": "rectus femoris",
      "b": "gastrocnemius",
      "c": "vastus medialis",
      "d": "vastus lateralis"
    },
    "correct_option": "a",
    "correct_answer_text": null
  },
  {
    "id": 27,
    "question": "How would you treat Fibrous Ankylosis?",
    "options": {
      "a": "friction",
      "b": "vibration",
      "c": "effleurage"
    },
    "correct_option": "a",
    "correct_answer_text": null
  },
  {
    "id": 28,
    "question": "Which connects muscles to bones?",
    "options": {
      "a": "ligaments",
      "b": "tendons",
      "c": "fascia"
    },
    "correct_option": "b",
    "correct_answer_text": null
  },
  {
    "id": 29,
    "question": "Which of the following is part of the Pes Anserine?",
    "options": {
      "a": "rectus femoris",
      "b": "gracilis",
      "c": "semimembranosis"
    },
    "correct_option": "b",
    "correct_answer_text": null
  },
  {
    "id": 30,
    "question": "Which would be the best treatment for acute Plantarfascitis?",
    "options": {
      "a": "friction",
      "b": "heat",
      "c": "ice and rest (because its acute) rest (because its acute)"
    },
    "correct_option": "c",
    "correct_answer_text": "ice and rest (because its acute)"
  }
]